<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
	<name>Humanlike Life Stages - Age Matters 2</name>
	<author>AliceTries</author>
	<targetVersion>1.0.0</targetVersion>
	<description>Adds a childhood and puberty system to rimworld that I hope you enjoy.
		----
		What?
		- Successor to Age Matters to be used with WooHooer or Children, School and Families, or not.
		
		----
		Why?
		This is my follow up to Age Matters mod, this mod hopes to fill in the existing gaps with progeny and representation. 

		After playing with a few other mods I've found that the aging of humanlike pawns doesnt feel right enough to me.
		- Children are handled weakly, not considered or are a burden on the community for 12 years which is twice as long as a colony lasts me.
		- Puberty is terrible, that really should be accounted for.
		- there is no real system to give Pawns secondary sexual characteristics beyond just that Breast mod. Which makes physical representation of gender very unfortunately uninteresting.
		- Gender indeterminacy is allowed for in the Verse engine but not used except sparingly by other mods which limits easily reachable transgender representation and transitioning.
		- Possibility create eunuch cast; again with the Verse engine supporting non-binary gender. Because why not?


		----
		How this mod works?
		- Maturity - Adds a HeDiff by age called Youth that degrades away into Puberty before becoming a full fledged adult.
		- Sex Organs and Secondary Characteristics - Added body parts for groin, chest and reproductive organs.
		- Adds a patch to fleshy Humanlike species to get reproductive organs and secondary characteristics.

		----
		Included Integrations :
		B19 Avian Races - https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1514158118
		Call of Cthulhu - Elder Things - https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=882126182
		Androids - https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1204079337
		Tree People - https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1403998409
		Cactaceae - https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=974612964
		avali - https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1314474881
		More customizable from settings menu.
		----
		Alternate parts:
		Sex Organs:
		testes, womb and ovaries, unidentifiable intromittent organ, unidentifiable ovarian organ, Ovipore, Spermatheca,
		Spermatophore, Pleopods, Cloaca, Ovotestis, Sporophyte, Gynoecium, Stamen

		Secondary Characteristics:
		Pubic Hair, Body Hair, Flower Petals, Leaves, Bark, Plumage, Scales, Goo, Sporing Body
		
	Enjoy - Alice</description>
	<url>https://steamcommunity.com/id/AliceTries/myworkshopfiles/?appid=294100</url>
</ModMetaData>